<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>measures on Suburb Zero  ACT</title>
    <link>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/tags/measures/</link>
    <description>Recent content in measures on Suburb Zero  ACT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.suburbzeroact.au/tags/measures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>why?</title>
      <link>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/the-pressing-need/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/the-pressing-need/</guid>
      <description>How is #ClimateChange affecting Australia &amp;amp; New Zealand?#IPCC author Michael Grose explains findings from the #ClimateReport released in 2021.
Since the early 20th century, the climate in Australasia has warmed by around:
🌡️ 1.4°C | 2.5°F Australia
🌡️ 1.1°C | 2°F New Zealand pic.twitter.com/YRDMCvpUq5
&amp;mdash; IPCC (@IPCC_CH) September 20, 2022 This proposed pilot program would assist a whole community to make the switch; that is, generously subsidise and support participating households to go electric in six important ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a world-first pilot program</title>
      <link>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/about_the-_programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/about_the-_programme/</guid>
      <description>This proposed pilot program would assist a whole community to make the switch; that is, generously subsidise and support participating households to go electric in six important ways. &amp;quot;By electrifying households, deploying even more rooftop solar, and installing household batteries, these emissions can fall to zero – that’s real zero, not net zero – by the end of the decade&amp;quot;. Well said, @GriffithSaul!https://t.co/TLwG4FnqGM
&amp;mdash; Brighte (@brighteAU) October 12, 2022 The exact details of the program are still being determined, but could look something like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>other initiatives?</title>
      <link>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/relations-to-other-programmes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/relations-to-other-programmes/</guid>
      <description>How do we fit in with other initiatives?
Suburb Zero Pilot and the National Electrification Program (NEP) The smart-energy transition and household electrification will lead to lower bills, fewer emissions and more jobs.
I advocate an Australia-wide National Electrification Program (NEP), starting with a demonstration project in Canberra to create the world’s first fully electrified suburb, to be developed in conjunction with Saul Griffith and Rewiring Australia.
The ‘Suburb Zero’ trial would see $20 million of federal government funding leverage $50 million of private sector capital for a two-year, opt-in pilot program that guarantees participating Canberran households a 20-25 per cent saving per year on their fuel and energy bills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>six things to electrify:</title>
      <link>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/six_things/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/six_things/</guid>
      <description>Six things to electrify: Rooftop solar Solar panels mean your home can generate its own power. Rooftop solar electricity is about five times cheaper than grid prices. A home battery Solar panels can charge up a home battery while the sun shines. Then the battery can help power your home through the evening. (You&amp;rsquo;re still connected to the grid for cloudy days when you need more energy.) Cooking Induction cooking uses around half the energy required by fossil fuel methods.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
