<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Learn on Suburb Zero  ACT</title>
    <link>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Learn on Suburb Zero  ACT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>why?</title>
      <link>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/the-pressing-need/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/the-pressing-need/</guid>
      <description>We need to decarbonise quickly. The intensity and number of floods and fires in Australia is on line with predictions from past climate models from the CSIRO and IPCC. A lot of dedicated clever people have strived for decades on the science of climate change. These models have been constantly refined and tested against reality.
“It is unequivocal that human influence has warmed the atmosphere, ocean and land” – IPCC Sixth Assessment Report</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a world-first pilot program</title>
      <link>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/about_the_programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/about_the_programme/</guid>
      <description>Saul Griffith argues that ClimateChange mitigation is an investment.
“You’ll end up saving a huge amount … in Australia, we would be saving about $40 billion a year by the end of the decade if we go down this electrification route.”
&amp;quot;We can achieve 50% emissions reductions by 2030 in our domestic economy by investing in households and small businesses, and they are real, achievable emissions reductions...&amp;quot;#climate #energy #auspol #hydrogen https://t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>electrify everywhere:</title>
      <link>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/electrify_everywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/electrify_everywhere/</guid>
      <description>Let’s electrify everywhere! Let’s electrify everywhere! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>other initiatives?</title>
      <link>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/relations-to-other-programmes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/relations-to-other-programmes/</guid>
      <description>How do we fit in with other initiatives?
Suburb Zero Pilot and the National Electrification Program (NEP) The smart-energy transition and household electrification will lead to lower bills, fewer emissions and more jobs.
I advocate an Australia-wide National Electrification Program (NEP), starting with a demonstration project in Canberra to create the world’s first fully electrified suburb, to be developed in conjunction with Saul Griffith and Rewiring Australia.
The ‘Suburb Zero’ trial would see $20 million of federal government funding leverage $50 million of private sector capital for a two-year, opt-in pilot program that guarantees participating Canberran households a 20-25 per cent saving per year on their fuel and energy bills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>six things to electrify:</title>
      <link>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/six_things/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/six_things/</guid>
      <description>Six things to electrify: Rooftop solar Solar panels mean your home can generate its own power. Rooftop solar electricity is about five times cheaper than grid prices. A home battery Solar panels can charge up a home battery while the sun shines. Then the battery can help power your home through the evening. (You&amp;rsquo;re still connected to the grid for cloudy days when you need more energy.) Cooking Induction cooking uses around half the energy required by fossil fuel methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Further reading?</title>
      <link>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/further-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.suburbzeroact.au/about/further-reading/</guid>
      <description>Keen to know more. See more. Hear more.
Best start with the book, ⚡️The Big Switch Audio Edition⚡️
Today we release📢
⚡️The Big Switch Audio Edition⚡️
Read for you by legendary Australians.
Chapters read by @RachaelHaynes, Tom Hickey, @PatCummins30, @_NicolaBarr, @AceBuchan, @YaelStone, @AliciaQuirk, @MariekeDCruz, and @ChristineMilne.#Climate #Auspol #ElectrifyEverything pic.twitter.com/2ffVRjPii7
&amp;mdash; Rewiring Australia (@RewiringAus) May 19, 2022 And then some press.
Saul Griffith @RewiringAus says #ClimateChange mitigation is an investment. “You’ll end up saving a huge amount .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
